I want to shout out to y'all for doing what y'all need to do with my stand-up dates because y'all
are getting them tickets. However, in Amanda We Trust shows, y'all ain't doing what y'all need to
do. I get questions and DMs all day long with people saying, I don't know what to do about
this government. I don't know what to do about these elections. I feel like I just now, I don't
have enough information. That's why I'm creating this space because I want us to be working in
community to inform us. I want us to be learning and laughing together about all the shit that we
don't know that we need to know. So tell a friend, tell a friend, tell a friend, come on out to Chicago
on January 19th and 20th. And Amanda We Trust live is going down at the Den Theater. Get your tickets
at amandaseals.com so we can all get our minds together while we're together on what to do
moving forward together. Yes, you had it. You did it. I heard you say it.